<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Federico Scodelaro</title>
    <link>https://pudymody.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Federico Scodelaro</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pudymody.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting my room with WebVR</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2017-03-13-painting-my-room-with-webvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2017-03-13-painting-my-room-with-webvr/</guid>
      <description>Intro This month im moving to a new house, and one of the questions that came out was &amp;ldquo;Which color should i paint the walls?&amp;rdquo;. I thought it would be nice to have some kind of &amp;ldquo;prototype&amp;rdquo; in which i could see how good selection a color would be. I inmediatly remembered that Aframe its the new hot topic, and with a panorama photo, you could see it in 360 degress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making images with an excel file</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2016-09-07-making-images-with-an-excel-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2016-09-07-making-images-with-an-excel-file/</guid>
      <description>The other day, i was with a friend and after a few beers, the idea of resizing every cell to a 1x1 pixel size in an excel file and styling its background to match a pixel in an image came out. Loving to make apps and script without any sense, i decided to make a web app who would do it. So this post is going to be about its making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a soundboard maker</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2016-04-24-making-a-soundboard-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2016-04-24-making-a-soundboard-maker/</guid>
      <description>The title is a little &amp;ldquo;metaish&amp;rdquo; (making a maker), isnt it?. Nevermind, this all started because with my friends we are use to play the sound when you level up in the MuOnline game whenever someone of us did something stupid. One friday night, i was so bored that i made a little soundboard with sounds of the game, you can read the source but if you are going to read this post, you will see it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first drinking coding game in JS</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2016-03-03-first-coding-drinking-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2016-03-03-first-coding-drinking-game/</guid>
      <description>Its been a long time since i write my last post, so here we are.
Currently im on my holidays and i want to play some drinking games, but i couldnt find anyone who mix the fun of resolving some js problems while you drink. I only found one similar which is called Crash and compile but it has to be played manually. So i thought, &amp;ldquo;why dont i build one who makes everything easier?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making our first Firefox OS App (NoCrop)</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-09-27-first-firefox-os-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-09-27-first-firefox-os-app/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve currently made a submission to the firefox marketplace, so whenever its available i will post the link here
Browser version
During the last months, there is a new trending type of images at least in my social networks. What are they about? They are square photos, with the main photo centered, and in the background the same image blurred. Dont get it? Here you have an example
How and why are they made?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a weather widget with es6 and flexbox</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-09-18-weather-widget-es6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-09-18-weather-widget-es6/</guid>
      <description>Today we are going to create as the title suggest a weather widget with some es6 features and the flexbox model. You can view the demo( currently it loads Argentina weather ) to see what it&amp;rsquo;s about or see the repository if you only want to read the code
First, we begin creating our index file with a simple structure, and loading the roboto font, and the normalize.css library.
&amp;lt;!DOCTYPE html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;html lang=&amp;#34;en&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;meta charset=&amp;#34;UTF-8&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;meta name=&amp;#34;viewport&amp;#34; content=&amp;#34;width=device-width, user-scalable=no&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Document&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;link href=&amp;#39;http://fonts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self hosted pdf viewer like issuu</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-16-self-hosted-pdf-viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-16-self-hosted-pdf-viewer/</guid>
      <description>In this post we are going to write a command line program which generates a version of the pdf viewer of Issuu. Here you can see an example.
First of all you need NodeJS, i think there are a lot of posts teaching you how to install it. Then we need to install GraphicsMagick, under windows this is done by an installer, on linux i think you have to add some repositories, but you could google that, there are lots of results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating an edit-in-place in AngularJS</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-11-creating-an-edit-in-place-in-angularjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-11-creating-an-edit-in-place-in-angularjs/</guid>
      <description>Today we are going to create an edit in place directive for angularjs. Here you got a demo so you can see what it&amp;rsquo;s about or if you already have some knowledge about angular and just only want to read the code here its the repository
So, lets start building things. First, we need a simple structure for our project, and angular attributes so we can bootstrap it.
&amp;lt;!doctype html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;html lang=&amp;#34;en&amp;#34; ng-app=&amp;#34;App&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;meta charset=&amp;#34;UTF-8&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Document&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script src=&amp;#34;https://ajax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recreating Tinder swipe effect with css3</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-09-tinder-like-swipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-09-tinder-like-swipe/</guid>
      <description>Today its a rainy day here and you cant do so much things on a rainy sunday, so we are going to recreate the tinder swipe effect with the power of css3.
First of all, i know you like seeing the final effect before reading the post, so here you got it and if you want just to read the code here you got the repository
First we begin creating a simple html structure for our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving from sublime to atom</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-08-moving-to-atom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-08-moving-to-atom/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post, so im all ears to suggestions.
I have been using Sublime since i have memory, but i wanted to try Atom beacuse his community seems so promising and the best thing its open source. So here i will write a little roadmap of some steps i&amp;rsquo;ve made.
Ui Theme I&amp;rsquo;ve tried the default ones, but then i remembered a tweet i read from Addy Osmani with a beautiful theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first atom package</title>
      <link>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-08-my-first-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pudymody.github.io/blog/2015-08-08-my-first-package/</guid>
      <description>There was one thing that prevented me from making the change. When you autocomplete a snippet or an emmet expresion, and you type the final semicolon, it is inserted although it had been inserted by the snippet. Sublime handles this excelente moving the caret next to the char, but in atom it is inserted two times.
Sublime: Atom: So i being open source and with a large community, i couldnt stop from writing an extension to handle this thing, so here it is for everyone who also wants it</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>